Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
I considered you more than a brother...
...entrusted my son to you.
However, an ambush took you apart
from me.
Ahmet...
I swear on Ahmet that...
...I will establish justice.
I stopped because you told me to do so.
I will set their tents on fire.
I will destroy the castles
they conquered.
Atabey...
...was in the same position as you
for me.
This is now a blood case, father.
Don't worry, son.
Firstly, we will weaken them with policiy.
If they don't give Turgut to us...
...we'll perform more than
what we talk about.
I have known Osman for years.
He will never leave things to chance.
So dig out Ahmet's body right now.
We'll save him from Osman.
Also, we'll take him to Nikea and
hold a funeral as he deserves.
Are you sure Osman will come?
We should never let our guards down.
Darkness is always with you.
If he comes, finish him.
Come on.
My Bey!
- My Bey!
- Tell me, Baysungur.
As you command, I have been following them
since they left the tents.
They buried Ahmet.
My Bey!
Excuse me...
We are riding horses after a dead man.
What do you expect to find?
The dead speaks...
...when the living stays silent.
Come on Alps!
Hurry up!
Hustle your bustle!
I was suspicious until now.
But now, I am sure.
They are afraid of that
even the dead might tell something.
My curiosity has been satisfied, my Bey.
Atabey dies
Cobanoglu buries.
Byzantine digs out.
When it is about the future of Turks...
...all the devils come together!
Let's go.
Come on Alps.
My Bey!
Duck!
Attack!
Baysungur!
Since Atabey...
...we haven't been able to fight
back to back.
You missed me, right?
O Allah!
Soldier!
Our duty is to take this body away!
Come on!
Take it!
Come to me.
There must a sign.
As those dogs want to hide him
from us...T
...there must definitely be a sign.
Take him...
...to the tents.
Come on!
Cobanoglu Ali and Osman will
fall out for each other.
This is inevitable.
Osman's blood is enough for all of us,
Romanos.
This revenge is all of ours.
They will splinter.
We won't stop
in the opposite case!
Our moves will continue until
Osman is removed.
So let your soldiers stay tight.
I will need them.
I'll come back again.
Cebe.
What is the reason of this
disrespect of your soldiers'?
If you try to leave here
before Cebe finishes his words...
...the cold Mongol sword might
cut your neck.
We talked what we had to talk.
We set our plan.
You took your share of gold.
What do you want me more?
Osman.
Defeating him in his tents is impossible.
He will come to me.
Osman is a wise man.
We can't drag him here easily.
Remember that we are playing
against a devil.
The devil...
...is me, Romanos.
What is your plan?
We'll gain trust first.
The time has come.
Aktemur.
My Bey.
Sit there, will you?
Sit on your father Gunduz Bey's place.
Come on.
Son, you will take care
of your father's heritage.
His post is now yours.
My Bey...
...my duty is to be worthy of
my martyred father and you.
Our hearts beat the same.
Our target is the same.
Eyvallah
(thank you).
Hay Masha Allah (praise be!)
You will do well in your post, Aktemur.
Now that you have the post, the command...
...we will call you Aktemur Bey
from now on.
Masha Allah (praise be!)
Masha Allah.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come!
My Bey!
Other tribe Beys want to see you.
So you are not the ones who
are in need.
Let them come.
Do you see what's happening, Selvi?
Do you see the trouble
Osman led us?
He is not even aware of his mistakes
because of his pride!
Osman leads not only himself but also us
to the cliff!
Listen to me.
Do not turn your back to Osman Bey again.
Just calm down.
Osman Bey must have a plan.
Don't you trust your Bey
as much as you trust Osman Bey?
Do you hear what you say?
What are you talking about, Barkin?!
I always trust you!
Don't you see that I stand with you?
Then do not question my words.
Stand with your Bey.
I stand with you.
But it is my duty to tell the truth
to my Bey, to my lover.
I haven't done anything wrong!
I do not do it for myself.
I'm doing what I'm doing in order to protect
you and my tribe, my father's memento!
Do what you need to do.
Stand with your Bey.
Now choose one.
Kizilbeyogullari tribe or Kayi tribe?
Osman is leading not only us, but also
all the Turkmen tribes to trouble!
Tell me Hatun! Do you choose
Kizilbeyogullari tribe or Kayi tribe?
If you want to care your tribe
like me...
...you will stay in Kayi tribe and
provide me with information.
Welcome.
Have a seat.
Bey's tent is a council for consultation.
You express your opinions here.
Obviously...
...there is something that worries you.
Tell me.
I am listening.
Osman Bey, the situation that we contrasted
with Cobanoglu Ali Bey isn't good at all.
You are right.
Not good at all.
He came to stand with us,
but now he stands against us.
My Bey!
Ali Bey is very close to Sultan Alaeddin.
If this case goes to Sultan Alaeddin,
we will be in a great trouble, my Bey.
Should we have been afraid,
stepped back and delivered Turgut Bey?
No.
The court will make the decision.
No matter who you are contrasted with,
even a Bey, or a Sultan...
...there is only one truth.
The right will not change
when there is an obstacle.
I even doubt what I saw.
We cannot judge by what we have heard.
You are talking nice and easy, Konur Bey,
but the infidels are building up an army.
We had a power against them with Ali Bey.
But now, we don't have Ali Bey.
Let the court serve the justice.
Then, Ali Bey will return from his
mistake and support us again.
Don't worry, aghas.
You speak truly.
We lost a great ally.
Who will benefit from this?
Surely the enemy.
But we'll talk about this at the council.
And make a decision.
For that reason, you can go on now.
It's Mongols who raided
the caravan.
And then, Cebe came to us.
We don't know who did this.
But we know the time.
So, keep your eyes on Cebe.
As you order, my bey.
They can plot all they want.
They can try to divide us.
But we don't have much time.
We'll take Yenişehir before the
emperor comes to Yenişehir.
Come on.
Yenişehir.
Allah is eternal.
Allah is righteous.
The steel makes more
sound than you, smith.
Which one of you is teaching
the other?
Give me patience!
Look at me, maybe I should strike
you instead.
Let's see who makes more noise.
Do you want it?
Allah is eternal.
Allah is righteous.
Smith.
Smith. Are you new?
We wander around realms and
serve whoever needs it.
Pack your things up.
What is it, brother soldier?
Why are you packing him up?
Not just here, monk.
All the smiths and armorers in Yenişehir
will be taken to the castle.
We serve our lord. Sure.
What will they do with so many?
All the horseshoes will be repaired.
Weapons too.
Enough talking. Pack your
things and get to the castle.
As you order.
They are gathering a big army.
For a big war.
We need to inform Osman Bey
without wasting time.
What are you waiting for?
Move.
Allah is eternal.
Allah is righteous.
Write everything I say.
My sultan.
I'll handle it!
Osman went over his level.
He is protecting the murderer of Atabey
Ahmet. He is breaking the order.
He is proving his ill-intention.
We await your orders to do
what's necessary.
Choose the fastest horse and
take it to the sultan.
As you order, my bey.
Father. My wound is alright.
I want to see Barkın Bey.
For what?
He is on Osman Bey's side.
My atabey trusted him a lot.
What will he do?
If Osman Bey protects that murderer,
what can Osman Bey do?
Isn't it better to make Osman Bey
lonelier?
When Barkın Bey stands with us,
he'll be lonely.
I'll do everything to avenge my atabey.
Don't doubt it, Barkın Bey will
be our ally on this.
Good then.
Go but test Barkın Bey first.
Then come and talk to me.
Don't try to do something on
your own.
As you order, father.
-Şamil.
-My bey.
Tell me. What's the situation?
It's an arrow wound, my bey.
But the arrow was poisonous.
It affects the mind.
It's not deadly.
That's why he is still sleeping.
So, they didn't shoot to kill
but to stop him.
When will he wake up?
It won't take long, inshallah.
He took the antidote.
He'll be at his feet soon.
Thank you.
Kumral Abdal taught you well.
Thank you, my bey.
My bey.
Cebe and his warriors are here.
They have captured Mongols.
Osman Bey...
...a part of the rebels are here.
These are just a few of them.
Let them stay here.
I will go after the rest.
Are they those who attacked Ali Bey's
caravan?
They are rebels.
They are only trouble for the people.
I don't know which caravan they looted.
You wouldn't give them to me before making
them talk.
Stay back.
Osman Bey.
Turahan.
It is fine.
Everyone screams about what they have
done but...
...whisper what they couldn't.
No matter what I did, I couldn't make them
say a word, Osman Bey.
I hope you can.
Turahan.
Take them to the caged tent.
As you order, my Bey.
Now, if you will excuse me...
...I will go after the rest of the rebels.
If there is any news that will help me...
...do not withhold it from me.
What benefits you benefits me too, Osman
Bey.
We have a common enemy.
All of you will be caught by Osman.
I will deliver you.
When we are done with Osman...
...all of you...
....will be rewarded.
Much gold...
...many horses.
They will interrogate you.
They will make you bleed.
You won't talk.
They will starve you.
I am sure of it.
Drink!
Drink as much as you can!
Come on, hatuns! Bring the goods going
to Söğüt here!
My Bey.
You had doubts about Cebe.
Has it increased or decreased?
No.
You can never trust them.
He gives you his leash but watches
your hand.
Thus...
...we will be on alert.
As you order.
Our friend Cebe is setting the game.
Osman is near his end.
He can't escape anymore.
I want to see Osman die more than
anything, Romanos.
Know that I can't wait for it.
We all want this.
All of us.
Besides, you being one of us helps our
games.
Even Osman doesn't know but...
...I am closer to him than his shadow.
And I will never leave his side so as to
be the first one to see...
...when he dies.
This is exactly what we need.
You should always stay with him so that...
...we can be informed of everything
he does.
If we are going to pull the ground under
Osman...
...first, we must know which ground
he will step on.
I am with him so that we do know.
We will know.
We will.
By the ninety-nine names of Almighty Allah
who does when he says "Be"...
...and fills our hearts with the light
of faith.
In the name of Allah.
Ali Bey turned his back on us.
And emperor is sending a huge army to
attack us.
Everything seems to be against us.
But...
...none of this...
...will stop us from conquering Yenişehir.
Osman Bey.
I have been fighting for you all these
years.
Before all...
...I know you are a cautious person.
Now, while Çobanoğulları Beys aren't
supporting us...
...while a huge army is coming to attack
us...
...is it time for conquest?
I take a look and see that...
...all beys are wondering about this.
What is the rush?
This is the greatest precaution.
Emperor Andronikos...
...gave the Yenişehir district to me
himself.
Now, he will settle the army there.
To strengthen his defense.
How do you know this, Osman Bey?
I know how to think with the mind of
my enemy.
I am guessing.
So, the reason for our rush is...
...taking Yenişehir before it gets
stronger.
Yes, it is.
Now, an army is coming at us.
But it is not the time to be afraid and
hide.
If we hide...
...we will face worse consequences.
But, my Bey, you have two castles.
We could gain the upper hand with
defensive warfare.
My Bey.
Barkın Bey.
I grew up apart from my Bey due to
my duty.
I grew up in the castles.
I disguised as the infidels.
But I never forgot something...
...that you also know very well, Barkın
Bey...
...defense is essential only when defeat
is imminent.
It is never a preference.
Attack...
... if possible.
Aktemur.
Praise be! You are a befitting son
for your father.
Thank you.
If everyone sees fit...
...if Osman Bey lets as well...
...I will go to my tribe and talk to my
beys at once.
Osman Bey, we support whatever your
order is.
You've supported me all this time.
Go back to your tribe now.
And start the preparations for the war.
Here you go.
Let's see those prisoners.
I hope it will be a healthy and mannerful
child, Bala Hatun.
Amen!
Thank you, my Servi.
It is beautiful.
Was I this little too, mother?
Sure!
You were a little baby.
You were like an angel.
My Ayşe, are you all right?
Zehra, give her some water.
Ayşe?
Here, Ayşe Hatun.
It must be that you haven't eaten
today.
Should I prepare you some food?
Would you like to get some air, Ayşe?
Aygül, is there any news from the beys'
gathering?
It is not over yet, Malhun.
Ali Bey leaving us wasn't good at all.
I wish Osman Bey would deliver Turgut Bey.
You know Osman Bey, Servi.
Let alone his brother Turgut Bey, he would
never deliver anyone without a trial.
Also...
...I don't believe Turgut Bey would do
such a thing.
Turgut Bey is a smart man. He wouldn't
make a mistake like this.
You know what happened before, sister.
The truth comes out sooner or later.
I hope so.
We lived and learned our lesson,
thankfully.
We did.
Whoever couldn't stand Ali Bey's support
to Osman Bey...
...must be involved in this.
Protecting Turgut Bey until the truth is
revealed...
...is Kayı Tribe's debt to him.
You are right.
Tugrut Bey and his tribe have always been
here for us in our darkest days.
We owe them much.
What is this?
Open the door.
Boran.
Brothers.
Is there some weakness in this tribe?
How do they poison the prisoners
in the tent?
We didn't let a bird fly, my Bey.
They are the guardian alps, my Bey.
These brothers were on the duty.
Tell me.
Tell me, alps. How could this happen?
We are ready to take our punishment for our mistake, my Bey.
But I swear no one came in or got out,
my Bey.
Then how could this happen, brother?
Stop, Boran.
Stop for a second.
Alps.
Alps!
Look at my face.
I fully trust you.
Obviously, there is something else behind
this.
Do you think it is Cebe, my Bey?
We will see.
We will see, Cerkutay.
Brothers.
Since I thought you didn't fulfill your
duty, I got angry.
Excuse my anger.
I have never seen my father this angry,
brother.
It is because of betrayal, brother.
If they were poisoned while in tribe...
...it means there is a traitor among us.
But who would want to kill a rebel?
I don't know brother. Time will show
the rest.
My father didn't give Turgut Bey.
He didn't but...
...this will have a price, right?
Of course, there will be, brother.
But you know what our father taught us
before fighting.
He who gives a sheep today gives his,
flock tomorrow.
-Who gives his alp, his brother...
-...gives his beyship.
Since the guardian alps didn't do it...
...they can't be poisoned in our tribe.
No one among the guardian alps would do
this, my Bey.
We raised all of them ourselves.
Either they have been poisoned before...
...or they have poisoned themselves.
Can we trust that Mongolian
commander, Cebe...
...who brought the captives?
The captives he brought in the morning...
...died in the evening.
Even the Seljuk Sultan cannot be trusted.
But...
...why would he poison the captives
he brought?
If he was going to poison them,
why did he bring them?
He wants to earn our trust.
That is why.
But...
...he didn't let them talk.
He is obviously up to something.
Keep your eyes on him.
Increase measures.
Can I come in, Bey father?
Come in, darling!
Come here.
I am sorry to interrupt.
Don't mention. Here you go.
My girl.
Konur.
Aktemur.
Turgut Bey will go to the castle tomorrow.
Increase the measures.
Don't let anything happen to him.
As you order, my Bey.
-Will you excuse us?
-Sure.
My baby.
I wanted to see you before I go to sleep,
father.
My darling.
My baby.
Did my sword begin to be forged?
Look at this!
My beautiful girl. Don't worry.
The most beautiful of swords will be
forged for you.
Of! Of! My children! My children!
This longing doesn't end!
Oh, my Kayı, oh!
I wish my Kayı was here to eat all
the food.
I swear I wouldn't say anything.
Of! Of!
Cerkutay!
What are you crying for? Your voice echoes
through the tribe.
You bored and bored and bored
the children.
Now they don't come back!
Yes, Cerkutay. Yes.
Is it even time for their return?
Not your children but you are bored,
obviously.
Yes, I am!
I am bored!
What kind of highland is this?
My children are captives there!
I am longing for them.
Do you know what longing is?
Cerkutay, get out!
Don't get me mad!
But...
...if we had another child...
...he would always be with us.
He would always be by our sides.
Right, my beautiful hatun?
Stop, Aygül! Stop!
Calm down!
Breathe!
Think again.
Again.
Get out, Cerkutay!
You mad man!
Kızılbeyoğlu Tribe
No time has passed since the conquests.
Will the people never rest?
The horse's hooves that go fast are thrown
in four directions.
The Turkmens couldn't get used to
this yet.
We shouldn't look for anywhere else while
we haven't settled here yet.
Your beys said. They are right as well.
Do you have anything to say, Barkın Bey?
Osman bey is great.
But he is a dreamer.
He tries things he can't afford.
We've always said.
Right?
Praise be, he managed all his duties.
But...
...Osman Bey doesn't see Yenişehir as a
conquest.
He sees it as a property fight.
He says if we don't make Yenişehir a home
for the Turkmens...
...we will lose what we have.
You say...
...we haven't seen peace and he says...
...we won't have an eye to see it if we
don't take Yenişehir.
You say the horse's shoes fall...
...he says there will be no leg to run.
Beys...
...When Osman Bey says something,
you should think twice about it.
Now we will wait...
...and think.
After a while, we will convey our decision
to Osman Bey.
Those who attacked Ali Bey and killed
Atabey are the same.
Although their disguises change,
their causes do not.
Thus we will be more careful going to
the castle.
-As you order, my Bey.
-As you order.
Turgut Bey.
Now they will try to attack you.
Let them if they can, Osman Bey.
But I don't understand why these dogs
disguise as Kayı alps.
Why do they choose this way?
The Mongols are of course involved.
But they can't handle this alone.
We have someone who knows his business.
And as if that wasn't enough, they are
taking the hypocrites with us.
Do you think Atabey is involved as well,
my Bey?
What will it gain them by killing their
own allies?
Let's say Atabey is a traitor.
But wouldn't it be beneficial for them
to be alive when he infiltrated us much?
No.
We are now on bad terms with Ali Bey.
This was what they wanted.
Now the Çobanoğulları will get the other
beys' support too and...
...point us as the enemy.
They sacrificed Atabey Ahmed to stop
our struggle to be united.
Ali Bey is a good man.
He has a pure heart.
But even he was deceived by their dirty
games.
Of course we know about their games.
But even Ali Bey cannot see the truth
because of these traitors among us.
Whoever this is, he is very close to us.
And he hides himself so well.
But we will find out.
Of course, we will find out.
Thanks to you, Turgut Bey.
Thank you.
Barkın!
What are you doing here? Everyone thinks
you went to the tribe.
Servi, I don't have much time.
Have you got any important news?
Servi?
I did.
They are taking Turgut Bey to
İnegöl Castle.
I know Osman Bey would do such a mistake.
Barkın.
Malhun is my sister.
You won't do anything that may harm them,
right?
I am not doing anything, my Servi.
But Osman Bey is very skillful at
attracting trouble.
Not only himself but also...
...he drags the tribe, us, your sister,
after himself.
Selvi.
Don't be sad.
Don't worry.
I won't do anything.
I will be silent for now.
I'll wait.
You see?
I think about our tribe and
Osman's reputation.
I know, my bey.
I know that you won't do wrong.
Where is he?
Where?
Welcome, Barkın Bey.
Barkın Bey, what's the situation?
Osman Bey is secretly taking Turgut Bey
who tried to kill you, to İnegöl.
Osman Bey...
do you think it's that easy?
İnegöl, huh?
You know what to do...
but be quick to gather
your men.
You will be rewarded, Barkın Bey.
I never forget a favor.
Alps, come on!
What will we do, my bey?
We'll wait, Hüsamettin.
We'll wait.
Allah is eternal.
Maybe we should stay away.
He seems to be angry.
If the father is a brand,
the children should be water.
His anger will soothe.
Father, we came to help you.
Orhan. Alahaddin.
Come here then.
Get your hammers.
Hold it.
My children.
Allah is eternal!
-Allah is eternal!
-Allah is righteous!
Ya Allah!
Allah is righteous!
-Ya Allah!
-Allah is eternal!
Allah is righteous!
Wait now, my children.
Wait now.
Tell me, my children.
What makes the steel strong?
The powerful strikes.
Only that?
The water too.
My children.
You will take the weapon first...
warm it up...
it'll turn aestuous...
then, you'll start forging it...
you'll forge it...
you'll forge it,
and you'll forge it!
And you'll leave it to cool down.
But you won't forget to
speak Allah's name.
That also will always be
with you.
So, you will have a companion...
and you will have a good weapon.
Only the brave enemies are
afraid of a weapon.
Only those who face you with
their arms.
Otherwise, this weapon has no
meaning.
Who else?
The treacherous backstabbers?
Yes, son. Yes.
But only one weapon works
on them.
Smart.
It's the word of our ancestors.
Even if your enemy is coming
with a stick...
you'll bring a steel shield.
My children, come.
Come now.
You'll always be cautious.
Victories won't make us careless.
Our sleep is the sleep of a rabbit.
Carelessness can stay away.
Mashallah.
We'll sharpen our weapon
that is the smart, father.
Mashallah to my valiants.
Mashallah.
A wolf's child is a wolf, my bey.
Mashallah to my bey's children.
My bey, beys want to speak.
Let them wait.
-I'll come soon.
-Yes, my bey.
When the foal grows up,
the horse rests...
when the children grow up,
the bet rests.
My children.
You won't leave here until you
turn this steel into a weapon.
This steel will be Fatma's weapon.
Come on now.
Yes, my bey.
Thank you.
I hope it's good news.
My bey, good and bad comes
from Allah.
We are just messengers.
Tell me, what's the result
of the council?
They abstain, my bey.
They say prosperity, comfort,
resting...
their hearts are with us but
their minds need convincing.
We are running out of time.
We have to solve it soon.
After this trial,
that will be done too.
Beys are waiting.
I'm going now.
The only thing that will be done
is you, Osman.
Behold! Osman Bey!
Go on.
You are also opposed to my Yenişehir
move, just like Barkın Bey's beys.
Now, tell me...
I'm listening.
A council is for the opposition,
for exchange of views.
Even if there is nothing else,
the people are unsafe.
Your greatest commander Gündüz Bey
is a martyr.
Turgut Bey is wounded.
Ali Bey who came to aid you
is now against you.
Osman Bey, you only speak
of your victories.
What about the losses?
The missing?
Demir Bey is right.
My bey, we know your vision.
We don't want to root here.
But the people are tired.
Osman Bey, Turgut Bey's trial
should be over.
There should be peace with
Ali Bey. We should regather our strength.
Then, tell us to ride and we'll
ride to hell.
But we need to wait now.
It must be a while since Gencebay
went.
Do you think he's settled, brother?
He was with Osman Bey
longer than us.
His training is complete.
He must be fine.
Incoming! They have Seljuk flags.
Open the gates!
This is what concern us, my bey.
After this smoke cloud goes,
we'll go anywhere you say.
Thank you.
I listened to you without
uttering a single word.
But I'll speak briefly.
My move isn't desperate for persuasion.
Jihad doesn't happen with persuasion.
Now, before the emperor moves
with his army, I'll take Yenişehir.
When I spur my horse, I won't
look behind.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come in.
A commander came from Konya.
He wants to see you.
Let him in.
Welcome.
You took a long road.
Come, rest here.
Osman Bey, I don't have much time.
I'll return before my horse's
sweat dries.
By Sultan Alahaddin's order,
I came to take Turgut Bey.
Asking the impossible doesn't fit
a smart soldier.
It's not asking, Osman Bey.
It's the sultan's order.
Asking or ordering.
It doesn't make the impossible
more possible.
The trial will be here.
Osman Bey, you speak as a revolter.
Don't make me use force.
Behold!
Now...
send my thanks to Sultan Alahaddin.
But we will solve our internal issues
inside.
If you mean to use force...
you can't even reach Konya to
carry the news.
The emperor is coming for you.
When it's so soon that you'll
beg for help from the emperor...
you are revolting against the state
for a criminal.
Here, I'm the bey.
And I'm the state!
Now get out of my sight!
You did your job.
Now go and carry the bey's answer.
I know Konya and Kayı.
Do as I say.
Don't push it.
So, you are the fool who turned
his back to the state to obey a bey.
Watch your words.
And keep your eyes on the truth,
commander.
Go to Konya now.
You are playing with fire.
Yes. We are the fire.
Don't get too close.
Go.
What will happen now?
The situation isn't good.
The sun blinded you.
You are stuck in the dirt.
You can't get out.
There is only one move to make.
And it's Yenişehir.
Either you are with me,
or you are with no one.
Good day!
Good day, sisters!
Thank you!
Alaca, is people's provisions
ready?
Everything is ready, Malhun Hatun.
Mashallah.
People will lack nothing
before the eid qurban.
Then, let's be on our way
and do our duty.
Sister, let me come with you
to Söğüt.
I want to have my part
in this good deed.
I'll go to the tribe
on the return.
Sure, sister.
Come on then.
Ayşe!
Ayşe! Ayşe!
Enough!
Do you want to die?
You are pale again!
Let's go to the infirmary.
Come on, to the infirmary.
Ayşe!
Aygül, what happened?
I speak but she doesn't listen.
You talk to her!
She keeps working.
She was about to faint.
Don't do this to yourself, Ayşe.
You didn't speak a word since
Gündüz Bey has fallen.
You are tearing inside instead
of outside, Ayşe.
You don't pity yourself,
what about your child?
Girls, bring some water!
Malhun, it's time.
Go to Söğüt.
We'll catch up.
You are right. We need to be
there for salaat.
Come on, women.
Ayşe.
Come on.
Alps. We are on our way.
She is powerless.
Let's go to the infirmary.
She doesn't want it.
You don't pity yourself,
what about your baby?
Baby?
Ayşe?
Allah's grace!
But why didn't you say it
all this time?
Is it something to hide?
Ayşe didn't want it.
But it's time, sister.
Gündüz Bey's gift.
Thank Allah!
Come on, Ayşe.
You should protect your baby.
To the infirmary.
Come on, let's leave you to
the girls.
Come on.
I'm going to İnegöl but...
I don't feel good about it.
We are doing what we need
to do for justice.
Be at ease.
With all the trouble we have,
now we are facing the sultan.
I'm afraid that he'll take Söğüt
and İnegöl after all the trouble.
Because of me.
Where we stand is justice
and truth.
It doesn't matter where
they stand.
Surely, my bey.
Surely.
Osman Bey.
I know that you protect me.
But allow me to surrender in Konya.
I'll return alive, don't worry.
I'm sure of myself.
Turgut, for sultan to see the truth,
you won't surrender now.
So, you will go to İnegöl.
If I surrender you now...
then, I'll be betraying
justice and truth.
The trial...
will be held in İnegöl.
Osman Bey has spoken.
Then, we should go to İnegöl.
My bey.
News from Kumral Abdal
and Master Davud.
It's bad news.
There is an army in Yenişehir.
It might move any time.
What are your orders, my bey?
We'll be working soon.
Be careful, Ayşe Hatun.
You are tiring yourself too much.
Your pregnancy is certain now.
Mother?
Is it true, mother?
My sibling...
Do I have a sibling, mother?
My beautiful mother!
My father's gift.
You...
is this why you were silent
all this time?
Why didn't you tell me, mother?
Cry, mother.
Cry.
Crying isn't shameful.
Your crying isn't from rebellion.
It's from longing.
Don't leave us without you, mother.
Who else do we have?
Aktimur.
Aktimur!
Tell me, mother.
Tell me.
-My son.
-Mother!
My son!
My beloved mother!
I was so afraid to not hear
your voice again.
Thank Allah.
I couldn't be sure earlier.
I didn't want to believe it.
When the midwife told me,
I ran to the tent...
but I couldn't find your father.
I couldn't!
I'm so much in pain.
So much.
I couldn't speak out of fear.
All that time...
your father and I wanted
a baby.
We waited for that...
but your sibling couldn't
come in time for your father.
My light...
my sunlight.
He couldn't...
know his child.
He couldn't see...
It's a trial, mother.
This is our trial.
But don't worry.
I'll protect my sibling.
I know, son.
I know.
My brave son.
You shined my day with your
beautiful voice, mother.
Today is a holiday for me!
My beautiful mother.
Duty awaits.
I'll go.
But I'll come back to hear
your voice again.
May Allah protect you.
Thank you, mother.
Gündüz...
It wasn't destined.
You couldn't know...
couldn't see...
but we'll have another child.
You always wanted it.
Cerkutay is tracking, right?
He is.
Turgut!
You'll answer for killing my atabey!
You'll die in pain!
Turgut Bey moved out to the castle.
They are coming closer.
Let him come.
He is coming to his death.
Turgut moved out to the castle.
And Mustafa moved to stop them.
It's time.
Once Osman gets Mustafa's
blood on his hands...
no one can hold Ali Bey back.
Then, neither Osman nor the Kayı
Tribe will survive.
Mongols on the other side...
we'll remove Osman from these lands.
All the arrows point to one target.
Osman.
Even if he survives one,
he won't survive the other.
Cebe is impatient for it,
Commander Romanos.
He is waiting.
Right.
Let's not keep the Mongol
wildling waiting.
Who are you?
Who are you swinging your
swords for?
I'm talking to you!
For me!
My atabey's murdeer, Turgut!
It's time to answer now!
You all will answer!
A trap!
Alps! Attack!
Turgut!
Osman Bey!
Come at me, Osman Bey!
The game of the jackals last
until the wolves howl.
You want to take revenge, huh?
But...
but you are in my hands now.
You can't kill me. You are afraid
of my father, Osman Bey.
You can't touch me.
The traces lead to Söğüt.
It might be a trap, Cerkutay Alp!
Aygül.
Women.
They went to Söğüt to take
provisions there.
It's a trap!
It's a trap, alps!
I'm the heir of the Çobanoğlu Tribe!
You are naive.
You are naive, son.
But it's apparent that your
atabey played you.
I need whoever your atabey Ahmet
was working with.
No one deceived me!
Don't speak of my atabey's name!
I'll avenge him, Osman Bey!
I only answer to Allah.
But you will answer me first...
and then your father.
Since Gündüz Bey has fallen,
Ayşe was buried in darkness.
It's hard, sister.
What can be worse than
losing your lover?
Surely, it's hard.
But together, we'll take Ayşe
out of darkness, inshallah.
Inshallah, sister.
Come on.
Alps! Take position!
Selvi!
Selvi! Sister!
Sister!
Kill them all!
Are you alright?
I'm fine, sister.
I'm fine.
You were right.
There is no end to the enemies
on the borders.
There isn't.
As long as there are wolves,
there will be dogs too.
Alaca! We are leaving.
Come on, Selvi!
Selvi! Selvi!
Alps!
Follow those women!
I can't--
I can't breathe, Osman Bey.
Son.
It's apparent that your
atabey deceived you.
He tried slandering Turgut.
You are lying!
It's all your pride!
You want to be the head of the Turks.
You will do anything for that, Osman Bey!
Son. Look.
You don't know anything.
You are deceived.
Hang on, sister.
Hang on.
A little more.
Selvi!
Alaca, protect Selvi!
Women, today we either live
together or die together!
Selvi! Sister!
Sister! Sister!
Please, hang on!
I'll save you.
Selvi! I'll get you to the tribe!
Alaca, protect Selvi!
Hang on, Malhun!
Selvi!
Selvi, sister!
Please, hear me!
Please, don't give up!
Hang on, please!
Malhun!
Selvi!
Are you alright?
Mashallah, sisters.
You didn't leave any for us!
It's no time to joke!
We have wounded.
I won't, my wife.
I won't.
Run this way!
Alps, come on!
Come on!
Bring the carts!
Malhun!
Sister! Sister!
Please, hang on!
Hang on, please!
Malhun, you are wounded.
It's not important!
Selvi! Hang on!
Hang on! Hang on, sister!
Don't leave me!
Selvi!
Now, tell me.
Who was your atabey talking to?
When would he leave you?
Did he know anyone in our tribe?
You are lying!
My atabey wasn't a traitor!
Die!
Son.
Alps!
Take him to İnegöl.
Clear the way!
Hang on, sister!
Hang on!
Clear the way!
We have wounded!
Hang on, Selvi!
Come on! Alps!
Women, inform Ayşe Hatun!
She was trained by Mother Selcan.
No one is better than her.
Come on! Come on!
Hang on, Selvi!
Come on, sisters!
Slowly, slowly!
Hold it tight!
Slowly!
Malhun!
Alaca!
Take Malhun to her tent.
No! My Selvi is dying!
You can't do anything, Malhun!
No, Bala! No!
My Selvi is dying!
You can't help like this, come on!
-Selvi!
-Malhun!
Don't scare your children!
Let's tend your wound, Malhun.
Aunt Selvi!
Mother!
What's happening, mother?
I'm fine, my daughter.
Aunt Selvi?
Selvi will be fine too.
Fatma. Children.
Your mother is fine.
She'll be better after
we tend her wound.
You are fine, right?
Don't worry, Orhan.
Be with your sister.
Inform Barkın Bey at once!
She won't die, right?
Mother Bala?
She won't die?
My mother and Aunt Selvi won't die!
No, my pretty girl.
No. No.
Don't be afraid.
Your mother is fine.
She'll be better.
Your aunt Selvi also be
fine.
Orhan. Take your siblings.
Pray. Pray.
Pray and they'll heal.
Who did this treachery, Mother Bala?
We'll find out, son.
We'll find out.
We'll find out when your
father comes.
Come on.
Come on, sister.
Mother! Mother! You, my sibling...
Are you alright?
We are, my dear.
We are.
Don't worry.
Go to your siblings.
Come on.
You were right.
Osman is in great trouble.
The real game is just starting for
Osman, Commander Romanos.
With our plot, we'll take his life.
We'll provoke Ali Bey against
Turgut.
That shepherd will answer for all the
Roman blood he shed.
I'll rip his flesh out.
I don't want to wait any longer,
Commander Romanos.
There is just one thing that bothers me.
He learned that I came to Bhytinia.
And where my soldiers were.
How did he know that?
I need to solve this first.
What's in your mind?
Listen to me well.
İnegöl Castle
Kutan! Call the healer!
As you order, my bey.
Turgut!
Murderer of my atabey, Turgut!
You are a murderer!
You lived through all this but you
don't ask why.
You don't understand the scheme
because of your naivity.
You are still saying murderer.
You are a murderer!
Listen to me!
Many Turkish beys were destroyed
because of idiot sons!
But know that I won't hurt
Ali Bey because of you.
Son.
Come on! Where is this healer?
Murderer!
It's important for us.
Do your best.
Don't worry, my bey.
Murderer!
You'll live, Mustafa.
For the future of the Turks,
you will live.
Selvi...
Ayşe Hatun.
Selvi!
Ayşe.
Selvi.
You don't speak, I know.
But it's not like that.
Please tell me.
How is my sister?
After all this time, I would want you
to hear good words from you.
But it's not good, Malhun.
Don't say it.
Don't say that, Ayşe.
I'll see my sister.
Wait. Wait.
Your wounds!
Ayşe, I'll see my sister.
Malhun! What happened?
Are you alright?
How did this happen?
Osman!
She is fine, my bey.
I tended his wounds.
She'll be fine.
Get well soon.
I'll be back later.
Osman. My sister is severely wounded.
She is fighting death.
It hurts me to lay here.
After your wound heals,
we'll go.
Selvi.
Selvi is left to my from my father,
my uncle.
She is struggling, Osman.
My heart is burning.
Wait now.
Malhun.
Mother!
My children.
My children!
Look, I'm fine.
Don't be afraid.
She kept crying since
she saw you.
I told her that our mother is
strong, that she'll be fine.
Nothing happens to mothers, right, father?
Mothers are very strong.
I told you. If the children
pray for their mother...
nothing happens to their mother.
My beautiful girl should never
be afraid.
I'm fine.
My beautiful mother.
Alright, I won't.
She won't. She won't.
My daughter knows her mother.
Her mother is strong.
I know.
My mother and aunt Selvi are
healthy.
You didn't believe me when
you were crying, Fatma Hatun.
And mother...
with the sword my
father forged for me...
I'll make them regret doing
this to you and my aunt.
O' the healer!
My Allah!
Selvi! Thank Allah, sister!
Thank Allah!
Bala...
Water...
Thank Allah!
Bala!
My time is over.
But I have to say it...
I have to get your blessing.
What are you saying, Selvi?
You'll heal, inshallah.
Malhun. Is my sister alright?
She is. She is. She'll come too.
Don't worry.
Thank Allah.
There is no time, Bala.
Barkın...
Whatever Barkın did,
he did it for us.
He did it for our tribe, Bala.
For my father's legacy.
Not because he is evil.
Selvi.
What are you saying?
Barkın Bey? What are you trying
to say?
I told Barkın, Bala...
I told Barkın that Turgut Bey
was going to İnegöl.
Give me your blessing.
It's yours, sister.
It's yours.
But what did Barkın Bey do?
Barkın...
Barkın loves Osman Bey...
Ahmet Bey was Barkın's friend.
They were close.
But he wasn't deceived by them.
He didn't turn his back on Osman Bey.
Barkın isn't evil, Bala.
Know this.
I won't forget, sister.
I won't forget.
Tell me fully.
What did Barkın Bey do, Selvi?
Selvi!
Sister.
My beautiful sister.
Hang on, brother.
I'll be over.
It'll be over.
May Allah not test anyone with this.
What happened, Osman Bey?
Selvi Hatun.
Give me your blessing, sister.
You have mine.
You were my sister for years.
I couldn't protect you.
You give me your blessing.
She is wounded.
Inside.
Selvi?
Barkın.
My bey.
Get out.
Get out!
Go to Ali Bey.
And say that Osman killed Mustafa.
Barkın.
Thank Allah you came in time.
I couldn't, Selvi.
I couldn't.
I couldn't protect you.
-I killed all the irregulars.
-So you didn't take any captives again?
I don't understand, Osman Bey.
All the ones you brought were
poisoned.
They died without answering
anything.
I know, Osman Bey.
He drank poison when he realized
he'll be a captive.
He died when I was trying to
interrogate him.
If there is something behind this...
then consider your life taken.
There is nothing behind it, Osman Bey.
It's just Sultan's order.
I'll tell him about your help.
Are they all dead?
If you ask the Mongols,
they are all dead.
Who else would I ask?
I have a Byzantine.
Then why aren't you bringing him
instead of a corpse?
Cebe works for coins.
The Byzantine will be
worth a lot of coins.
Who is his owner?
Did he speak?
Rom... Roma...
Romanos!
Romanos.
So, Romanos rules all
the irregulars, huh?
I need that man.
Why is it so important for you?
Mustafa Bey was murdered.
Those who attacked him are
collaborating with them, obviously.
If the importance
is high, so is the price.
When I get him, you will get paid.
However Osman Bey wants.
You'll stand up, right?
We will leave this dire tent together
and go back to our tent, right?
You will go to our tent without me.
Take good care of my tent.
Don't turn your back to them.
Hang on, my Selvi.
Please.
Don't leave me.
Barkın Bey doesn't look well.
This much anger is not good.
Not at all.
I hope he doesn't do anything bad.
It's not easy, Malhun.
Not easy at all.
Malhun.
You should talk to Selvi.
She's said some things but...
if they are what I've thought about...
What did she say?
If you leave...
I'll be sad.
Don't leave me.
I bear witness that there is
no deity but Allah..."
"and I bear witness that
Muhammad is the messenger of Allah."
Selvi.
Selvi? Don't leave me.
Don't leave me.
Don't leave me, Selvi!
Selvi.
Malhun.
I couldn't protect her...
When a calamity befalls them, we certainly
belong to Allah and to Him we shall certainly return.
O, who believe in Allah. Don't betray
Allah and Muhammad.
If you do, you betray everything that is
given to you to take care.
Sheikh...
What is told in this verse? (ayet)
Bismillâhirrahmânirrahîm.
(in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
Here they are.
What is given to us are these.
Quran is Allah's sunnah.
However...
smart Muslims never betray.
There are smart and believing Muslims but
they betray Allah's sunnah anyway.
However, they don't even
recognize what they are doing.
They think Allah's bans and orders are...
...for only the jahiliyyah
(days of ignorance, before Islam)
...like there is no jahiliyyah
in the time we are living in.
They are mistaken.
Devil approaches them sneakingly.
Devil says: "times have changed...
...Allah's words was for those
times back then....
...now everyone does what they do
for themselves.
We are not intrested in anyone's sins
or virtues" The devil says.
He says: "Not my business".
A Muslim who says "not my business"...
... will betray the entrustment of Allah.
If a Muslim shuts his eyes to sins...
...and let it happen...
...it means he betrays
the entrustment of Allah.
But my Sheik, Islam is a
religion of latitude, isn't it?
No, my shahzade.
It is not, my Orhan.
Islam allows favour and beauty.
Islam doesn't allow the evil,
what Allah made Haram (forbidden)
Islam doesn't allow corruption, theft,
alcohol, gambling, adultery...
...the perversion of Lut tribe,
leaving the prayers and deceitfulness.
The more you allow the evil,
the more your life extends.
Islam does not let the evil live on.
Islam fights against it.
Nobody is more merciful than Allah to allow
anything that Allah does not.
Allowing what Allah does not...
...is a great arrogance.
This is shirk.
A Muslim must be on the alert.
You shall always stand against the evil.
Do not allow the evil and haram.
A Muslim does not allow the evil.
He interferes.
Do not be one of those who say
"not my business". Never.
May Allah prevent us from becoming
one of those, my Sheik grandfather.
May our Lord let us stay in His path.
Amen, sons.
May our Lord let you stay in His path.
Amen.
Tell me.
What news Barkın Bey sent to me?
I told you to tell me.
My Bey.
Your son, Mustafa...
Osman... his nephew... stabbed Mustafa.
What are you saying?
I told you to take care of my son.
Where were you while
Osman was doing all this?
Where was Barkın?
Is my son alive?
I don't know, my Bey.
They were taking him to İnegöl.
They killed my brother and
they stabbed my son.
I came here to support Osman...
he stabbed my back many times.
I swear that I will harm
his tent and İnegöl.
Go to the tent.
Send news to other tents.
Find everyone who is able to hold a sword.
From now on, we have no other
choice than war and revenge.
Ali Bey.
Bring your army.
Burn the tent.
However, you may not find
Osman Bey when you come.
What are you saying?
Osman is walking into a trap
that will end himself.
Romanos.
We met again.
I've told you we will meet again.
Don't worry.
We will settle accounts.
Thank you, Cebe.
You got Romanos.
- You did well.
- Yes, Osman Bey.
Osman!
You should have not come here.
A wolf never gives up tracing its hunt
even if it's in hell.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com